e
[Music]
welcome living Mana church family we are
so happy that you are here and we are so
happy that we are here
it has been three weeks it's been two
it's been two weeks but it feels like
three and I'll tell you why in a minute
but but it's been two weeks but it's
been too long that we haven't been here
with you in studio uh in person on
Sabbath and so we are thankful to be
here but we are so happy that you are
here uh today as well please put in the
chat where you're viewing from it was so
nice to it was a lot of traveling it was
a lot of ministry traveling um but it
was great to meet uh so many of you uh
we met some in Washington state in
Seattle area got to meet some in Florida
and Orlando area last week as well so it
was great to meet you in person it was
just it was just amazing experience um
but it is good to be back here with all
of you and worship here with you on
Sabbath here at Living Mana church so
please put in the chat where you're
viewing from so we can uh give a special
welcome to you and again if it's your
first time please put a one in the chat
yeah um I think we uh well we did share
the uh blueprint message part one and
part two part two and part three is
coming part three is coming we got
something different for today yes um
even our study on the 144,000 it's still
coming it's still coming both of those
will be uh part we did part one we did
so much travel we've done part one no we
did part one 145,000 and we did part two
this is a part three coming yeah yeah
yeah okay we did do part two this is
part three you're right see that was a
lot of travel guys all jumbled up in my
head right so part three is definitely
going to be next week um and then we
will do the blueprint part part three in
a couple weeks in a couple weeks so it's
coming so stay tuned so stay tuned stay
tuned okay so we have Terry Parker from
Lacy Washington welcome we were just in
your beautiful state a few weeks ago we
have ilila in North
Carolina all right brother
good to always see you um Tiffany and oh
Tiffany and Ringle Georgia of course
Tiffany hi Brit family always good to
see you guys um all right and viewing
from St Johnsbury Vermont and that would
be Andrew welcome welcome to living Mana
Church good to see everyone today got
lonia from Lancaster California welcome
I used to have family that lived in
Lancaster haven't haven't been there in
a long
time all
right happy Sabbath to everyone we have
again Washington
State it was so good it's so beautiful
guys Seattle is really beautiful it is
so so beautiful Mount reneer wow
Majestic it is beautiful absolutely
beautiful it was a great great beautiful
uh weekend and Ministry trip that we
were able to spend and again got to meet
some of you there as well so all right
we got Brooklyn New York welcome to
living Mana Church
Barbados amen so good to see all of you
I'm just excited again to be with you
here live and um just want to let you
know that mental health Mondays is back
as you guys know we had our second part
to our depression series and we're going
to do a third part because you guys had
so many questions and we didn't even get
to them all so we're going to carry that
into a third part and thank you for
tuning in please come back and bring uh
somebody with you so that's uh this week
um we're looking forward to that on
Monday at 700 p.m. central also want to
let you guys know that registration will
be opening for the convocation on
December 1st that's right December 1st
is when registration will start so again
we're having put a one in the chat if
you are excited yes about that cuz we've
been talking about it for for a little
bit but it's happening it's happening
and registration will again open up on
December 1st and that will be on our
living Mana um website so you'll be able
to do that we'll give you more
information um as each week we're going
to give you more information about that
and to remind you so we are again just
excited about um the convocation and
like we got to meet you guys some of you
like in these last two weekends as we
were traveling and that was just uh
amazing and great um but I can't I can't
wait to where it's just more of us
together um and we get to to meet all of
you so all right I see all those ones
I'm glad you are excited can't wait to
meet you there um and you will get more
information but prepare for December 1st
and again it's May 1st through 4th so
that's that first uh weekend in May that
we will be in Orlando Florida together
for our first convocation
all right t-shirt message uh forwarding
all isues to heaven and this is not a
new shirt this is one that I've had for
a couple of years and so you guys have
seen it before but um it never fails to
um to just be so powerful every time I
choose to wear this shirt that you know
again most of my messages are about
faith because that's what the Bible
That's because most of God's message to
us like he God just wants us just to
have faith right he's like look and he
says it in so many different ways in his
word and he's like please have faith
give me your burdens give me your
problems give me your sins have faith in
me and that's what he wants us to learn
so most of my t-shirts are going to be
about faith and the the Bible is
teaching us to have faith he will work
everything out he works even our sinful
characters he works that out
us he does all that he wants us to have
faith to completely on him and I can
tell you that this week has been no
different of challenges and having to
forward all issues to God and what we've
been talking about um is learning how to
forward them immediately because telling
you guys stress is not your friend it's
physically not your friend it it it can
you if you stress you're you're
suppressing your immune system and
disease can pop up because your immune
system is your a disease fighter you
need to have a strong immune system so
it's not your friend for your physical
health it is absolutely 100% not your
friend for your mental health when we're
stressed areas in the brain that should
not be activated or activated and we're
behaving as if we are in um some serious
life danger situations and we're not but
our behavior is like that and our body
just stays in this uh very stressful
place and our and it's it's not mentally
healthy we don't make good decisions we
don't respond well in our relationships
and I can go on and on and talk about
this so my point is is that stress is no
way is your friend the unhealthy stress
is no way your friend and it's not
helpful to you so the way to avoid
stress is to forward all issues to
heaven right away y we don't need to sit
with them they just need to yeah send
them away amen yeah situation happens
and then send it off send it off send it
off all right that's the message for
today yeah okay so we got a huge Sabbath
School ahead of us today yes we do so we
are pray and jump in or you want to
introduce it now yeah well I'll
introduce it and then we'll pray okay uh
so we're going to be talking today about
prophecy and uh as we all know major
events happened this past week yes it
did major major events and um you know
everyone's kind of like okay so what
does this
mean um we have a lot to cover today a
lot to cover so and if we have a do a
part two we will yeah go ahead and share
this link cuz we're going to be talking
about Revelation chapter 13 the second
beast of Bible prophecy Robin I like
that say no to babysitting stress I love
it that's good that's good I'm gonna use
it I'm G use it with some some clients
I'm gonna use it for myself I'm gonna
use it for myself so okay let's go ahead
and pray and uh and then we're going to
jump in okay all right Heavenly Father
um we just uh come before you today Lord
lifting this uh Sabbath School service
to you Lord we're praying that um as we
go over Bible prophecy Lord as we
refresh
um our minds uh on what you have said in
your word Lord um please open our eyes
give us wisdom and understanding Lord
help us to catch a bird's eye view of
what is happening we pray in Jesus name
amen amen amen amen all right go ahead
you all share this link let people know
let people know um we're talking about
Revelation chap 13 and what I want to do
today is uh we are going to get uh in a
plane and we are going to take a high
view a 30,000 foot view of what's going
on okay a lot of people don't see what's
going on or understand what's going on
because they're on the ground MH and
when you're on the ground in the midst
of it when you're looking at it from a
Earthly perspective right it is very
difficult to see the big picture mhm and
so we're going to we're going to soar
high today and we're going to check out
we're going to see without a shadow of a
doubt what is going on prophetically
speaking so um we're going to go to the
screen and uh we're going to begin with
Revelation chapter 13 verse 11
Revelation 13 verse 11 and verse 12 so
here's what the Bible
says says and I beheld another Beast
coming up out of the Earth and he had
two horns like a lamb and he spake as a
dragon verse 12 and he
exerciseth all the power of the first
Beast before him all the power of the
first Beast before him
so we understand from Bible prophecy
that this beast in Revelation 13:1 that
comes up out of the earth uh having
horns uh like a lamb and speaking as a
dragon uh
represents
America and
specifically it
represents Protestant America right
right so it's not just talking about The
American Nation it is more specifically
pointing to protestantism within America
and what I want you to note
here is that the the uh the prophecy
says that this Beast would exercise all
the power of the first Beast all the
power of the first Beast
so what does that mean he exercises all
the power of the first Beast it means
what the first Beast did whoever that
first Beast is he does the same
thing so we know that the first Beast
according to Bible prophecy represents
uh the papacy during the Dark
Ages we know that the papacy was a
church State entity and as a result of
the papacy being a church State entity
it persecuted so the Bible is telling us
that in
essence this second beast Protestant
America protestantism within America
will eventually do the same thing that
the first Beast did religious
persecution right um but there's
something that I really need us to focus
on and and it is something else that the
first Beast does so what else does the
first Beast do let's go to Daniel
chapter 7 ver 25 and note what the Bible
says here speaking of this little horn
power which is identified as the first
Beast it says he shall speak great words
against the most high and shall wear out
the Saints of to the most high and think
to change times and laws and they shall
be given into his hand until a time
times and the dividing of time now
typically when we look at this uh verse
in Daniel 7:25 we we understand that the
little horn changed the law of God right
and we typically focus in on that um but
there is not a lot of talk about the
little horn changing
times so what is the Bible talking about
when it says that he will think to
change times and laws again a lot of us
think oh we're talking about the time uh
of the Sabbath right the time of the the
the only time that's found in the
Commandment but there is something else
we need to
understand during the Dark
Ages when
protestantism
began um
when protestantism began to
pinpoint the papacy as the Beast of
Bible
prophecy one of the ways they identified
the Beast of Bible prophecy was through
counting prophetic times
MH they saw that the little horn was to
dominate for a time times and half a
time and they calculated that time
period to be a day for year and thus
they looked at the papacy and they said
no other power has dominated for this
long over you know hundreds and hundreds
of years of domination at the time so
you must be the
power and as a result of this and almost
all Protestants all Protestants were
United on this prophetic time this is
the papacy right so what the church did
what the papacy did was it actually
sought to change
prophetic times
M um let's go back to the screen and
here's what you will
see the Catholic Church came up with two
new schools of prophecy two new schools
of thought
prism and
futurism prism said know these times are
a day for day not a day for year right
it's a Day for year meaning it's three
and a half literal years and this
happened in the past it's already done
while PR while futurism said no uh this
happened in this happens in the future
it's three and a half literal years and
it happens in the future it can't
possibly be us it's not us y'all right
the enemy is somebody in the past Nero
the enemy is somebody in the future but
it's not us now this was meant as a
decoy so put that word in the chat for
me please This was meant as a decoy to
take the prophetic finger off of the
actual enemy and point them redirect
them someplace else hey it's not me look
over
there now at first protestantism was
like that's funny we're not looking
anywhere we know you are the one
M go to any Protestant church today go
to any Protestant church today and ask
them about the
Antichrist today they're going to repeat
to you futurism right it's in the future
three and a half years or prism it was
in the past so I want you to check this
out the first Beast used a
decoy to take the finger off of itself
and point to another enemy a non threat
a non-existent enemy
no no no no no it's not us it's somebody
else and at first protestantism which
was God's
main
vehicle for truth was like no we're not
falling for that right but
eventually after
centuries protestantism bought into
capitulated to and
adopted the decoy
all right so y'all put a one in the chat
if you're following thus far what I just
laid out yes because what I'm about to
what I'm about to show you is that the
second
beast does the same
thing apostate
protestantism will
exercise the same power that's what the
Bible says the Bible says he exercised
all the power of the first Beast the
first Beast had power to create a decoy
and take the prophetic finger off of
itself MH and point to an enemy that
wasn't really the enemy MH the second
beast we are going to see does the
exact same
thing all right everybody following mhm
again put a one in the chat if you're
following if this makes sense now
remember the second beast speaks like a
dragon and the dragon represents Satan
how does the dragon speak the dragon in
fact John 8:44 the Bible says you are of
your father the devil and the lust of
your father he will do you will do he
was a murderer from the beginning and
abold not in the truth because there is
no truth in him when he speaketh a lie
he speaketh of his own for he is a liar
and the father of it when the dragon
speaks the dragon Lies when the dragon
speaks the dragon deceives when the
dragon speaks the dragon sends out
decoys when this lamb or this Beast that
has horns like a lamb speaks it is
speaking lies therefore one of the
things we can expect from apostate
protestantism
is to
create
decoys that are designed to remove the
finger from itself I want to say
this but do they know that they
are that's what I that's what I'm trying
to say they don't know that they're um
the cath setting decoy that's right the
Catholic Church they think they're doing
God's right service they think they're
doing God's work yes because because
what those horns like a lamb so it's
very it's very Christlike it's very it
looks Christ it looks Christlike this is
the key thing you guys understand that
when the Catholic church when the
Jesuits of the Catholic Church came up
with these two new schools of of
Prophecy prism and futurism they were
genuinely trying to
disprove that they were the Beast of
Bible prophecy right so it's not what
they were it's not like they were like
well this stuff ain't really true but
we're just going to use it as a decoy no
or we are intentionally working with
Satan or we're intentionally working
with Satan so we're going to no they
genuinely thought hey you know what we
just found the answer this is why we're
not the Beast of Bible
prophecy it's some it's Nero in the past
or it's something in the
future it is the same
thing with
protestantism protestantism is not like
hey what we use as a decoy they are
genuinely being
misled in creating these decoys but the
devil is
intentionally putting out these decoys
to turn people's minds from who the
actual Beast is who the actual enemy is
at the end of time according to the
Bible all right are y'all following yeah
does it make sense notice again with
me great controversy page 445 when the
leading churches of the United States
uniting upon such points of Doctrine are
as are held by them in
common shall influence the state to
enforce their decrees and to sustain
their institutions then Protestant
America will have formed an image of the
Roman hierarchy and the infliction of
civil penalties upon the centers will
inevitably result it is clear here
that we're told that it is the leading
churches of the United States uniting
upon such points of Doctrine now when we
hear points of Doctrine we typically
think oh state of the dead or oh um you
know Sunday
sacredness points of Doctrine here is
anything that we can use that we hold in
common that will
unite all of us
together so that can be social issues
right that can be cultural issues MH
these are all points that are being
used points that they're holding in
common to unite them
together and I would say that the most
craziest thing in the world would be for
Adventists to actually unite upon common
points held by the churches that are
designed to bring about a unification
MH that prepares the way for what we're
reading in Bible prophecy
M we're going to see what these points
are what was this going to say like you
need to be um a little more clear a
little more clear on what that is
because um you know yes we're we're
Protestant you know we're all
Protestants right um but even what
evangelicals you know believe we're not
evangelicals we're not we're
not but I we're about to see I think for
sometimes for some avenus that's for
some that's hard
to for them to tell the difference
difference yeah and it shouldn't be so
we're GNA in this Sabbath School we're g
to we're going to kind of jump back to
some things we've shared in the past
because I want you to know everyone that
the stuff we have been sharing over the
last 3 4 years the things we have been
warning
about mhm let me say this up front cuz a
lot of people are
wondering you know is this is this it is
this where the mark of the beast is
going to be implemented and I'm saying
we don't
know I it's Nuance what I'm say what I'm
saying up front is I am not saying this
is it y'all I'm not saying that so
please this is not a false alarm this is
not a oh you know this is what
Christians are going to do over the next
four years I am not saying that at all
it is possible yes but I'm not saying
that it's going to happen if y'all have
heard my presentation on the Whirlwind
you know that it's going to take the
Whirlwind it's going to take Satan
appearing as Christ to actually bring
about right the fulfillment of this
prophecy the way I but and I let but let
me tell you if this is not a clear
indication of the direction that is
setting up America to
receive this deception then I don't know
what is right and yeah like you said um
and well this is the way I say it
another shoe still has to drop for it
all to come together before the mark of
the beast correct but this
is one shoe dropping one shoe is
dropping yeah the shoe is
dropping so check this out y'all
remember that uh in our past studies in
fact in the elephant in the room series
we we talked about something called the
New Apostolic
reformation and what the New Apostolic
Reformation is is a
movement that is Christian nationalism
and
prophetic in nature these are the
prophets remember we talked about the
prophets who were all prophesying of
what's coming in the government and how
Trump is going to be president and you
know he's going to have a second ter
were Trump proph were Trump prophets and
Trump prophecies and the whole movement
the New Apostolic movement was
surrounding the Takeover you know of a
government and and and and and how
Christians were going to dominate and
Rule and all these things right and of
course Trump wasn't elected right last
time around and some even argue that he
really was elected some people like this
is the first president to be elected
three times
because they are they're saying he
didn't lose the last election right so
that's neither here nor there the New
Apostolic
movement is a Christian nationalist they
believe in what is called the seven
Mountain
mandate so remember we had talked about
this in great detail in great details
so this is um this is what the prophets
and the head of this movement the ntion
the New Apostolic Reformation this is an
interview I want you to see what they're
saying about this election right what
they're saying is God did this and you
know what's Wild
and I'll be
honest the way everything went
down I
mean Satan is not unique but he can
sometimes be creative and crafty if you
will
because the way that it went down on
Tuesday the whole election I mean um
honestly I think Trump was surprised I'm
going be honest with you like so many
were so surprised at how it went down
and how he won um it would make it seem
like that is true it was it was divine
it look it would make it look like it
was if y'all have not seen the elephant
in the room series now would be a good
time to go back and watch the elephant
in the room series all right listen to
this we're going to uh we're going to go
to a clip here so want you to check this
out listen
up you know Psalm 3 three we talked
about it before the election that God's
eyes are upon those who put their hope
in his mercy and uh that's what we saw
and we also did the very things that
attracts God to a nation we appealed to
heaven we ask for forgiveness we also
gathered and we stood for the things
that God endorses the other thing that I
think was very powerful Pastor Jean we
said it on America stands is when you
saw those two um different camela who
was at the one rally when she denied uh
the Lord she said you're at the wrong
rally I believe at that moment God put
his stamp access denied he let him know
there is no way they're going to get it
and lastly two days later when uh JD
Vance uh Guy Yell out Jesus's King he
said yes he is access granted and now
we're going to turn a page and we're
entering into a new chapter of reset for
America and the United States of America
and I'm very excited about it yeah me
too me too and to all of you watching
flasho Army you guys uh this is your
Victory you guys rallied the last four
years you've grown in numbers but you've
grown in power and impact so you Relish
in what you did I think we were all
wondering what would happen in
Pennsylvania and as we all did our jobs
uh with Laurel Brooks the other day uh
we wrote and we saw what happened in
Pennsylvania that's something you can
say
okay so first clip and we got we got
several to go but as you can
see the Christian world looks at this as
this is evidence that God did this God
was in the mix here
and this is a
mandate these next four years m is a
mandate God has given us an open window
to do
some amazing
things okay I want you to we're going to
go to another video and and just watch
same same clip this is flasho USA uh or
Flash yeah flasho and I want you to just
listen to what else they
say the mission to restore America to
our judeo-christian values it continues
we don't just want Revival in America we
must have a Great Awakening to Christ in
every corner of our culture here in
America our Dream to reclaim America's
greatness is no longer a distant
aspiration it's an urgent
reality thank you for being a part an
essential part of this
Mission once again and what he said I
mean what he said is he doesn't even
know was like quote from from the great
I to say he quoted it I mean just return
to our judeo
Christianity like is that that's not my
Christianity not not their Christianity
I'm just what I'm saying is our version
of Christianity or what the Bible
teaches is different so they want so we
they're saying God wants to that's what
I'm saying wants to return it back to ex
theirs or his exactly exactly so in
every and he in every corner in corner
of the country of country what does that
mean what does that
mean what does that mean now if you've
read Revelation chapter 13 we know what
that means right if you've read the
great controversy we know what that
means
right but to them it's something
different right we're doing the will of
God yes now I need you to see this we're
going to we're going to keep moving um
so y'all remember let's go to the screen
do y'all remember this
sermon that that I preached uh sometime
back I'm sure if the sh God oh yeah yeah
yeah broken ankles yeah yeah yeah broken
ankles so in that
sermon I talked about how the devil will
Mo act like he's moving one way and then
get everybody moving that way and then
cut back the other way and you know
that's that in the b in basketball world
that's called the Sham God where you
fake one way you fake left
let's say but then you're actually
moving right right so
so I need y'all to catch what's going on
here let me let them talk first so
remember this now here's what I want you
to keep in mind as we watch these next
clips remember how the warning was
wokeism is taking over
America right um there's a Marxist
take over over of America there is a
communist takeover of America now if
these things were true if these things
were true you would almost expect that
when you when you when we got to the
election and you you look at the at the
election map the the electoral map you
would almost expect to see mirror in
that this this movement towards
Marxism and communism and you know the
overwhelming majority the the enemy in
America was that right
remember so let's check this out okay so
remember everybody including
many all Christians including many
Adventists were
like the marxis the Marxist communist
takeover of America is at hand now we
know according to Bible prophecy doesn't
warn us of that that the Bible talks
nothing about a leftist takeover of
America about a communist takeover of
America about a Marxist takeover it
speaks literally nothing of that not in
the great controversy not in the Bible
anywhere right because the Bible doesn't
talk about it the spirit of Prophecy
doesn't talk or the great controversy
doesn't talk about it but protestantism
in America was like
hey that's the enemy mhm every body
that's and they they trumpeted this over
and over again that's the enemy that's
the enemy that's the enemy and so let's
see let's see what happened in this
election let's see what the electoral
map showed us let's go to the
screen and one more thing like we've
said we'll never waver from proclaiming
those words Jesus is Lord and Christ is
King
so with that let's do a little look back
uh let me show you the latest
information on the Electoral College and
the latest I think we have a Graphic
there to show you of how many how many
seats are there so 312 to
226 uh and it's still not over uh this
is pretty much Mark I would say this was
a red
tsunami that we were looking for it
definitely happened in America what do
you
think yeah is a red tsunami I think one
of the interesting things is there are
maps uh with which are Arrow Maps which
have arrows all over them showing the
movement of counties in which direction
they moved red or blue the entire
country is red and it's absolutely
incredible one of my favorite moments I
saw in mainstream media was them looking
at a map trying to bring up everywhere
that Cala had outperformed Joe Biden and
there were literally zero counties this
is a red wave election it is a complete
and total rejection of wokeness radical
liberalism gender ideology and
CRT and I agree with what everybody else
said praise God this is a miracle it it
is a miracle let me show you another
miracle I can say this because I used to
live in California uh Pastor Chay on
look at this graphic of what happened in
California the difference between 2020
and
2024 I would say that's not even purple
that's leaning pretty heavily uh
red it's amazing it's the grace of God
okay so again I want you to see how the
chrisan world is viewing this red map
they just said America is
red
now remember this y'all what were these
very people
warning there's a communist take
happening in
America there's a Marxist takeover
America if that were
true number one we should be able to
find it in the Bible but lo and behold
it's not in the Bible now you would you
would have thought that we that
Adventist would have known better oh
yeah yeah that's just that's just a
decoy but no
thousands thousands of not only
Christians Across America but even
within our own church you would hear
this stuff from the pulpit this warning
of why we've got to
join with the common
points of the rest of
Christianity sham got it wait hold on
here's another one here's another one
that's here's the spe the spiritual heat
map right there it is see that Elon most
posted it so if you were looking at a
map of America you podcasters go to go
to my Twitter account when you get home
and take a look at it it's a vastly
expanded Red Zone now we've seen this
before the rural versus the city vote we
know that but what does it tell you from
a spiritual
perspective it tells you that
principalities and
Powers concentrate where populations are
the most concentrated it's kind of an
interesting thing how when Babel gets
built and everybody's in one location
it's easier you go to Washington DC it's
a spiritual environment you go out the
Hollywood it's a spiritual environment
it's as though the spirit realm comes
down upon the high concentrations of
people and then gets into the
institutions there as much as possible
to create a Blue Zone but what I'm
showing you here is the expansion of the
red and now look at this the realization
is if I showed you the updated map of
California you'd see it it's only La San
Francisco it's um it's the cities where
you could this is almost a heat map of
where the cities are which tells you
Mara Milla is saying this he's saying
the next phase of his evangelism work is
to go into the strongholds of cities and
the Lord told him to do this before the
election and so San Francisco boom la
boom New York City boom Trump went to
Madison Square Garden which was like a
spiritual act itself and surprisingly
the big flip is New York City is moving
towards Trump I mean that that makes
sense like 40% win on of of Republican
voters in New York City it's a it's a
big movement so these blue areas are the
concentration of power and money in the
in the city areas and this becomes a new
awareness for us that we've got to go
there with the gospel because the gospel
will actually have an effect on the
atmosphere it's hard to explain but when
Philip went to Samaria bam it affected
the atmosphere and the whole city was
filled with joy when that took place so
there's your spiritual heat map gives
you an idea doesn't mean that we've won
just means everything's moving in our
Direction in terms of the ideological
battle now is the church ready for
America's Great Awakening it started in
2016 and it's really three phases go to
the next uh Twitter post I have the
three phases it's like the three
so well to the Great Awakening and again
Great Awakening and what version of
Jesus what version of Jesus and by the
way note now how we don't we don't have
to take the gospel to these red to these
red spots it's already christianized
that's what they're saying now remember
this y'all how many of us fell for the
decoy how many of us got sham got it
into thinking the real enemy is the
Marxist when if we had followed the
Bible all along if we had followed the
prophet all along if we had just simply
stuck to our prophetic roots oh no we're
not falling for that no there's no
Marxist takeover of America no there's
no communist takeover of America no no
no no no no that that's that's all
madeup stuff come on let's go back to
the screen I want to show you one more
let's go back to the screen
and uh we're going to check this out
check this out here red dots and if
you're listening to the podcast here's
what we're doing the red dots are not
dots they're arrows oh what an
interesting graphic this is this is
where AI is such a gift to mankind
because this is a move a showing of all
the
3,143 counties in the United States and
whether they move to the left stayed
still or move to the right and the arrow
tells you how far to the right they went
and you know what we're looking at we're
looking at a migration pattern Mercedes
of thousands of counties moving to the
right the only place it didn't happen
and we have some circles here we have a
circle a real cluster of motion in New
York City oh my gosh 40% of Jews in
America that would traditionally be
voting here there independent they're on
the side of Sanity moving to the right
probably because of the
praza um Pro you know terrorist campus
uprisings which did a great job for
helping Trump make the argument this is
crazy and so you see those arrows are
close the only place curious enough that
the left had a stronghold that went to
the left further is around Stacy Abrams
Atlanta uh precincts so where you've got
strong concentrated blue money you've
got the move to the left that's that's
that's waro County Etc so you you could
see that that's the Atlanta suburbs with
the one place where Harris improved out
of the whole ocean of motion to the
right but look at those right arrows
folks if you can see at the podcast
shows it's like a flight pattern
everything's moving towards this
direction it's I say it's an IDE it's
it's almost like an ideologic graph of
how this is the mo This is Our Moment
frankly because if a house is swept
clean Jesus said it is in danger of
being recaptured and I promise you the
so what does he say this map is the
evidence that things are moving in our
Direction what have we been saying at
tante for the
last
five
10 15 are you talking about months years
oh years okay okay prophetically
speaking
MH we've been
saying hey guys the great controversy is
happening
Revelation 13 what we've always believed
is
happening but it it began to blow my
mind
how I was now hearing the very decoys
put out by apostate protestantism now
entering
into our own
churches beware of wokeism Beware of
Marxism 12 years beware of Communism the
government all this stuff where I'm like
wait a minute wait a minute what does
this have to do with Revelation Chapter
13 How are we getting sham
goded when the prophecy says this is the
way things are going no Pastor you're
wrong no Pastor no no no no you don't
get it you don't understand the real
threat you're being duped by the media
you're following the media wait a minute
the very people who have been warning
mhm that this communist take Coming to
America are now out touting look at how
everybody is with us
mhm they they think they
evangelized the majority of America and
they just have the cities and the
coastlines to continue to evangelized we
just have a little blue left on the map
MH this is God With Us don't you see
little Blues have the majority of the
people and I just wonder
how how many how many of us were part of
the Red Wave MH how many of us were
praying for a red wave wow wow wow wow
now the Red Scare put a one in the chat
if y'all know what the Red Scare
is the Red Scare is what they called the
Red Scare is what they
called um a communist Takeover in
America and it happened in the 20s it
happened in the 60s so there was a first
uh 1920s and the 19 there's a first wave
of Red Scare then the second wave of the
Red Scare and the Red Scare has been
pretty effective MH Communists are
coming into our country
beware join us why because the enemy is
communism there's been an argument of
Christian of American Christianity for
forever and this third time around again
Beware of the Communists the Red Scare
the red scary but you know what as
Adventists when we look at this map let
me let me let's go back to the
map uh y'all remember the
map let me tell you the real Red Scare
is not
communism the real Red Scare is not
communism the real Red Scare is what you
just saw on that map in which the
Christian world is T now listen there
are people who voted voted that way who
all they cared about
was you know they're not trying to
implement Christian nationalism they
just want whatever better taxes or you
know I mean lower high whatever they
want I I can't they just want this is
what I wanted I'm not even a Christian
but I want this so for whatever reason
they voted the the point is the
Christian World sees this as look you're
coming to us they are on our side even
if they don't agree with us
MH religiously they are on our side this
is our mandate this is our mandate to
implement the things we want to
implement for the best of our
nation and again Satan was able to use I
mean what makes it look so Supernatural
is that there's never been a political
candidate nominee I should say for a
party um that was it was convicted felon
that lives their life so opposite of
Christianity um but almost assassinated
twice twice yeah everything yeah it's
just like it um it looks like a miracle
God and it looks like a god it looks
like yeah a miracle it looks like God so
check this out we're going to go back to
the screen I want you to check this
out back to something that I said on
flas point when I started August of 2020
uh
and that was this in March of that year
I had a vision where I was taken up over
the Earth and I heard the most
authorative voice that I had ever heard
I don't know if it was a voice of the
Lord or an angel and I've shared this on
flasho and it said Divine reset Divine
reversals and I saw this shaft of light
hit this tremendous darkness and I think
that's what we're seeing is This Global
reset listen the globalists thought it
was their reset God said Nay it's mine
and then lastly in
2016 uh I sh he this again on flasho
where I had an experience where uh a
visitation of the Lord came and he said
to me he asked me a question and this is
so profound he said what does a nation
Hank look like filled with glory and I
looked up at him and I said I don't know
I've never seen it he said your eyes
will behold it and he said first though
there'll come great Transfiguration as
it was with my son when the glory came
he said but also he said when Glory
comes he said I will deal with
corruption and I will bring a reset and
I will show my mercy and I think we are
going to see that because the goodness
of God is always connected to his glory
and that's what we're seeing uh
beginning to play out this is a new era
and what we have to do is stay faithful
to God and watch what begins to happen
around the world uh on a incredible
scale of of the Lord's hand in it yeah
amen okay can I say this really quick
because you have so many great points I
just want to say this that like what
ainst know like before I mean let's put
it this way before I guess Tuesday we
couldn't trust the government but now we
can now now we can now we can okay and
avist know that something's coming
before Jesus comes I
mean that's basic foundational adventism
but not anymore but so so now it's just
this is this country they know good and
well they should know they should know
good and well that this nation is not
going to truly become a Christian Nation
before Jesus comes like what do they
think is happening it's not going to be
a Revival like that
yeah so I'm just I'm surprised decoys
yeah but I'm when you get caught up in
decoys the
vaccine or okay
rism all of these things were what was
coming from the mouth of the beast of
the Beast with horns of a lamb these
things we didn't originate them the
vaccine the government is out to they're
trying to shut down the churches they
after us communism Marxism all these
things came out of the mouth of the
second beast of Bible prophecy and
Advent is were like what oh yeah we GNA
take that battle up too or yes right now
here's theun and some are not like
consciously thinking like okay yes I
want their type of spiritual Revival but
when they think just about their own
selfish gain if you
will they were willing to be like okay
well if I go this route then
I'll even though all this other stuff is
would come with it but I could get more
money I I mean I'm just putting it out
there talking real talk and I and I saw
that from someone who actually is in the
tax
bracket that would get I mean they're
they're Millionaires and they they said
you know what I had to vote against my
own money even and I think that because
because of
ethical reasons that they felt convicted
on but what comes first the kingdom of
God or your comfort or your own
pocketbook yeah okay are you voting your
interests right or okay okay so check
this out
y'all listen to what he just said he
just said God showed
him that a global reset is coming now
remember this remember this y'all
remember
the global reset that the elites were
supposed to pull
off the elites are are implementing this
Global reset and they they're using the
vaccine this is the perfect opportunity
and now God just told him you know psych
they're not really put pulling it off
I'm going to do a great reset okay
listen y'all listen listen listen let me
go back to the screen do y'all remember
a sermon that I
preached a few years back called the
Great reset I remember all your sermons
okay in that sermon in the great reset
actually I don't remember okay I
remember the name but there's been 26
years of sermon so I can't in that
sermon about the great reset where I
talking about the supposed plot by the
global Elites yeah to
reset the whole world yes and they were
going to use the vaccine to do this yes
yes yes and then said listen that's not
the reset right that's coming the reset
that is coming will be a reset led by
Christian nationalism Christian
nationalists and here you have the
head these are the prophets of the of
the New Apostolic
Reformation who are saying God has told
us there's this is the beginning of a
reset
for America a good reset a Godly
um Let me show this let's go back to the
screen let's go back to the
screen here to discuss the impact of
Catholic voters on this election is the
president of Catholic vote Brian bur
we're so glad we got you back up online
uh welcome so so let's talk about this
because Donald Trump has been he's not
leaving anything on the table he's he's
posting s prayers to St Michael he's got
the ab and Maria going at rallies um
he's going to the AL uh Smith dinner and
he's like you know just really showing
love to Catholics and Kamala has nothing
going on in that and is that a huge
mistake it is I I believe so and you
know Camala Harris has made a massive
gamble here Rachel you know she has
calculated that she can build a new
political Coalition that excludes people
of Faith including Catholics and as you
know the the Democratic party has been
the home of the majority of Catholic
voters for for decades and yet what
we've seen is on issue after issue over
the last several decades a systematic
leaving behind of Catholics to the point
where Cala Harris is essentially now
saying uh I don't I no longer need you
and get out of my way well in fact her
campaign manager I mean she there
supposedly there were some tough tussle
about why she didn't go and she's
blaming her campaign manager and the in
essence the conversation was about that
the campaign manager said hey this will
offend our lgbtq and our our very
Progressive voters better you not go so
I I think your point is well taken I
want you to look at this poll this is um
with Catholics so Harris has 47 to 52
with Trump but here's another
interesting poll there um among all
that's among all Catholics but white
Catholics 61% uh for Trump only 34 with
Hispanic Catholics that that's an
interesting number especially as you're
seeing Hispanics men in particular
moving towards Donald Trump what do you
make of those
numbers well we're seeing even better
numbers for the president in some of
these swing States particularly in the
Upper Midwest like Pennsylvania Michigan
and Wisconsin where the Catholic vote
makes up nearly 30% and I think what we
might be seeing here Rachel is really a
watershed moment where this longtime
tradition of many uh Catholics voting
for Democrats have finally said uh I
didn't leave the party the party left me
and they are now looking seriously at
Donald Trump not just on a lot of the
obviously traditional social issues like
life and religious liberty but on the
border on the economy and on frankly
just our Catholic way of life I think
they feel comfortable with with
President Trump and they don't feel so
with Cala Harris yeah I mean she's been
very aggressive U against Catholics I
mean even as a senator right absolutely
as a US Senator she went after a member
of the Knights of Columbus uh she's
introduced legislation that would end
our Catholic Hospitals our Charities she
does not believe in religious liberty
for Catholics and I think uh we're
waking up to this fact this is a
different Democratic party than what
we've seen in the past very different
even from Joe Biden who at least paid
lip service to the Catholic issues and
called himself a devout Catholic uh you
know Catholics are kind of tired of
being catered to by politicians every
four years that come around with this
social Justice platitudes and they've
finally said enough is enough we want
someone to stand up for us stand up for
what we believe and I think right now
president Trump is that choice yeah you
know I think a lot of uh Catholics did
fall sway to sort of the social justice
especially when it came to the Border
they really wanted to show compassion to
the illegal immigrants who were coming
over many of them but as you know are
Catholic but so many have fallen into uh
exploitation sexual exploitation the sex
trade and even child labor that they're
seeing that these so-called Progressive
compassionate policies don't actually um
end up being that way so Brian bur great
to have you whoever's advising Donald
Trump Bravo I mean he's he's he's
hitting all the right notes Camala pay
attention Brian Birch thanks for
joining thank you so much you got it I'm
Steve duy I'm Brian kilme and I'm Angley
aart and click
here
okay
so he's hitting all the right notes m
um there's a lot that was said there
that is kind of like H but we're not
going to get into that right now I just
want you to see what were what were we
told Protestants and Catholics uniting
on points that they have in
common you look at how the Senate has
flipped you look at six out of nine of
the Supreme Court Justices are Catholic
and again I am not saying this is it all
I'm saying is watch the trend y'all
prophecy has told us where this thing is
going we have no reason to
be sh got it no I think this what is the
most interesting is that like honestly I
mean I was watching the
Evangelical talking points and vote but
the Catholic vote not as closely they
haven't always been so connected with
the Evangelical vote but on on this
election they were and that was the
surprising element Y and I'm just
thinking of an El white quote as I'm
speaking that and this is
why sometimes we'll look at what's going
on in public and we'll be like oh we
need to change our prophetic
interpretation maybe we were wrong I
heard a I heard you know somebody
talking about maybe we were wrong about
you know being so focused on apostate
protestantism maybe we should join
together you know with our Christian
brothers and sisters to fight against
these evils now listen y'all it it's
absolutely mindblowing how we can allow
what we see in the world to manipulate
what we understand prophetically to the
point where we no longer we've been
we've been following the decoys and
listen in that sermon the great reset I
talked about what Lucifer did in heaven
how the first thing he did was he had to
implement distrust in the government mhm
the government is out to get you I'm
talking about in heaven distrusting the
government they're taking your rights
they're not giving you the truth and
unless we take the government
over we're immediately going to be D
it's going to be very bad we got to do
this so they were able to implement this
Spirit of distrust
MH and that's how they gathered everyone
together okay but that's where project
2025 makes more sense now
that this is the playing field now
replacing the government with
like-minded people or with only
like-minded people that think and
believe like they do yeah that's the
plan of project 2025 that's the goal
that's the purpose of it so watch this
and now they can yeah check this out
check this
out how did apostate
protestantism how did apostate
protestantism do what how did they flip
this map the way that they did check
this out number one instilling suspicion
in the government and create distrust in
any news coming from it is that what
Lucifer did in
heaven make it appear that there is a
Sinister hidden plot to take away their
freedoms by the global
Elites
mhm creating an
atmosphere in which Liberty of
conscience appears to be
threatened make it appear that if
Christians don't act quickly to secure
the government imminent servitude is at
hand this is literally The
Playbook of what Lucifer did in heaven M
literally so come
on um
um in fact he captured the new sources
but our new sources should really be the
Bible prophecy wanted to be our number
one news source like just follow just
follow this blueprint just I'm telling
you how this is going to lay out and
what to do follow that that's right and
he kidnapped that's right the news
source that's right so listen y'all let
me say this clearly this is not about
Donald Trump and has never been about
Donald Trump it's not about Camala
Harris it's not about what president it
is about apostate protestantism that has
been my battlecry for years right Donald
Trump just happens to be in that
position position to do that it's not
about him
MH guess what his character is messed up
like a lot of our characters are messed
up right we're all Sinners we are we're
not talking about individuals here we're
talking about what the Bible says is
going to happen and the Bible is
pointing out
Babylon the mother of harlots and the
harlots
[Music]
together but when you get caught up in
personalities when you get caught up in
no well this is my team versus this is
your
team you missed the point all together
Democrats nor Republicans are Democrats
nor Republicans are ushering in the
second coming of Jesus they will be on
the same team again
ultimately they will at the End by
following the
decoy this is what administ would turn
this statement into great controversy
page 445 listen when the global Elites
you see it up on the screen okay when
the global Elites uniting upon such
points of vaccination wokeism CRT held
by them in common shall influence the
state to enforce their decrees and
sustain to sustain their institutions
then the global Elites will have formed
an image to the Communist socialist
secular Marxist hierarchy and the
infliction of civil penalties upon the
centers will inevitably result that's
what Adventists think
today reading this right it actually
says when the leading churches of the
United States not Global eles uniting
upon such points of Doctrine not
vaccination wokeism
CRT held by them in common shall
influence the state to enforce their
decrees and to sustain their
institutions
then Protestant America not the global
Elites will have formed an image to the
Roman hierarchy not communist socialist
secularist Marist hierarchy and the
infliction of civil penalties upon
desent denters will inevitably be the
result you guys
you got sham got
it if you're watching this not all of
you got sham got it but many God sham
got it it's okay let's heal the ankles
and let's get back to what God called us
to do right listen
listen um let's talk about the Seven
Mountains
mandate
and y'all need to see this y'all need to
understand what this thing is let let me
go to the video and check this out are
now having a real sober session I
promise you what they're saying is we
can't afford to have the radical baggage
of crazy left-wing ideas we will never
be able to to have an audience with this
going now that Trump has done a
realignment and let's face it it's a
trumpian alignment that means we it
doesn't sustain itself once that
personality is no longer there as a
galvanizing Force so we we have two
years three years four years with which
to impact the institutions and I want to
go there today yeah it's the seven
Mountain story your problem right now is
Harvard
okay so he just said yeah it's the seven
Mountain story M meaning it's the seven
Mountain mandate that's what we're
talking about that's what we need to
implement over the next four years this
is our window of opportunity this is not
some random guy speaking this is the
main profit of the New Apostolic
Reformation which has millions of
Christians following both on a religious
and political level because it is a
religio political movement and so this
seven Mountain mandate beloved it is
absolutely crucial let me go back to the
screen I'm going to read from Johnny
en's Eno's book The Seven Mountain
prophecy listen what he says in the
chapters of this book I will refer to
the foundations of culture or sector or
societies as mountains Revelation 17
describes a harlot who sits on a beast
with seven heads that are seven
mountains the Demonic entity described
as a woman must be displaced from the
mountain or seats or power this this is
our mission that we are commissioned by
Jesus to do Jesus is the head and we are
his body he already did his part at
regaining all power and authority
through the cross and his
resurrection another book impacting the
Seven Mountains from the courts of
heaven I'm just going to read the that
underlined section this implies that the
church which is the revelation of his
body is the earth in is responsible for
seeing these enemies brought under his
rulership we are here to subject all
enemies under the power of His lordship
through the authority he has delegated
to us now why is it so important to
understand why is it so important to
understand in Revelation 7:19 there's
the text hereis has wisdom the seven
heads or seven mountains on which the
woman
sits listen to
this what the seven Mountain mandate
says listen to this y'all they are
literally telling us what they're saying
is that these seven mountains are the
mountains of government the mountains of
media the mountains of uh the mountain
of
um
business uh the mountain of
religion uh I remember you did this in
elephant in the room Series in the room
series uh the mountain of Education yeah
and
um I can't remember we'll we'll get to
the seventh mountain in a moment what's
interesting and I don't know I don't
think we did this in the um project 2025
the mountain of family right but I'm
just curious you can find all those
mountains in Project 2025 right correct
that's what I'm getting to watch this
y'all listen up listen to this
Mercy they made that up right Revelation
179 is not talking about mhm these are
the seven mountains right entertainment
family business government they made
that up right the Tex is talking about
something completely different but not
what they said it is our job as
Christians to sit on top of that
mountain I don't know if y'all caught
that just now if you're sitting on top
of that mountain who does that make
you God that makes you the woman
okay
sorry they are literally saying we got
to get on top of that mountain okay to
run the government got it that's exactly
what Revelation 17 is describing this
religious power that is running the
government and and those that believe in
a seven Mountain mandate 7M seven
Mountain mandate are saying we got to
get to the top of this mountain and run
these govern these these mountains
they're literally
saying we need to be we need to run
education we need to and which means you
are that woman and the daughters
described in that prophecy and they
don't even realize what they're saying
now now listen here are the seven
mountains we put it up on the screen the
religious Mountain Family Values
education media arts and entertainment
business and government do you
realize do you realize real that the
way come back come back to the screen
with
me what do you
think was the
platform that created this Red Wave what
were they what were they
saying there's an imminent takeover
coming there's an imminent
takeover that is attacking Christ
Christianity religion M Family
Values our educational system and all of
that our educational
system the
media business your money the Crooked
government
literally their
platform was the seven Mountain
mandate now yeah there were some people
who don't care about religion but they
cared about
government hey I'm with you on the
government
Mountain there were some people who were
like hey I don't care about the
government but I do care about education
wokeism I'm with you on the education M
each one of these
mountains was a tool being used to
create a coalition that's how they got
there designed to put them at the top of
these
mountains
mhm the Mandate came from they pulled
from from each all the seven mountains
but not everyone believes in all of all
seven that's right some do but it's like
business is your thing and we got you
yeah entertainment is your thing we got
you
religion we got you MH it's interesting
that Trump didn't even know anything
about project 2025 and like this was
the play this was and they just happened
to match okay they just happened to
match wow check this
out check this
out let's just go through this very
quickly and let's see if if Advent has
actually got involved in fighting for
these
mountains let's see see so let's take
the religious
mountain in a religious
Mountain we they had to implement fear M
the fear of Marxism communism socialism
atheism
MH and man I I was just shocked as I was
hearing from our own pulpits and from
our Min Ministries that are supposed to
be professing and proclaiming the Three
Angels messages instead proclaiming the
Seven Mountains messages Mercy wow
Marxism is the
threat what about family values
yeah gay
marriage MH
abortion
transgenderism
[Music]
wokeism what about
education again what are they doing in
our schools and our
universities
socialism Marxism the liberalism you
could put wokeism in that too put
wokeism in there too critical race
Theory which they think is well I'm I'm
starting to hear Adventist ministers
Adventist people talking about critical
race
[Music]
Theory and how
Anglo someone some some I saw somewhere
that anglosaxon
protestantism is under attack in America
from ad from an Adventist Source
anglosaxon
Celtic
protestantism is is under attack in
America that that's our prophetic
message Mercy all of this is to pump
fear so what about the media yeah the
corrupt media man you can't trust what
the media is saying so we got to create
our our ex and Rumble and these
different sources of media because the
mainstream media cannot be trusted in
cannot be trusted
and with all the podcast I mean anybody
can be an official that's right media
source
and factual and believable
and it's just a free-for-all the art
arts and entertainment the Hollywood
Elites
business your wealth your money your
taxes the government there's a deep
State the vaccine was a part of a deep
State plot to turn over the government
to to to to lock down the churches and
all these conspiracies that were
supposed to happen over the vaccine and
guess what here we are in
2024 no lockdowns half the population
isn't
dead
and there were so many people that
bought into the vaccinate the vaccine
conspiracy that even when
nothing of any no many people are dead
the churches are are are shut down
people are so locked in that they're
like see now it's coming out all the
damage that was done over this vaccine
wait a minute what all what damage it's
almost like y'all just made stuff
up the vaccine is come and
gone but I got to cling to this
thing to prove that I was right where
are the
lockdowns where was the this is the this
is the perfect opportunity for the
global Elites to come
in and create this great Global reset
and your money's going to be taken away
from me and those who got the vaccine
are are going to now hate the Bible when
they read it and and all the stuff that
was supposed to happen and none of it
happened and instead of owning up and
saying yeah we got Shamu it no we're
going to turn around and blamed and
tried to point a finger at the church to
say all our conference leaders should
have done this and should have done that
really how about you confessing and
repenting from getting sham goded and
making a big deal out of something that
had nothing to do with prophecy had
nothing to do with Daniel chapter 3 and
those who stood up against the vaccine
were going to be the faithful Daniels
for the great coming lockdown that was
[Music]
coming what are you going to going to do
for the next four
years you can't talk about
Marxism you can't talk about the
government can't be
trusted you can't talk about the V you
can't what are you gonna do now praise
God they can only follow follow or fall
in line with the government
legislating righteousness or things
that it's supposed to be separate
in Christianity not meaning it should be
someone's individual decision not the
government telling them alen white says
to do that alen white
says many in our
church have come to see things so
closely with the
Enemy that when the time for the crisis
comes they are prepared to choose the
popular
route so many of us have thrown our back
in with Evangelical
Christians we've got to partner with
them and fight against these mountains
and y'all got caught up in the mount in
fighting for the seven Mountain mandate
thinking that what you were doing was in
the name of
righteousness how absolutely let me tell
you I was blown away by this red map I
was like wait
what MH
listen listen let me show you something
let's go back to the screen I I if we
can get another 10
minutes I know yes I do that publicly so
listen y'all but I think I know give 10
minutes I want to say this I think I
don't know this is me just saying this
but I almost think yes the red map is a
real thing I don't mean to interrupt you
but I think Co prepared people to I mean
just Co was so blew us all away and how
you know government had to come in and
do so many things to try to keep you
know the country running and safety for
our health and everything I think that
what happened there actually shook a lot
of people and just kind of maybe open
people's minds up
to these seven mountains yeah I think so
I'm not I'm not blaming Co altogether
but I think it was something that really
yeah just caused people to think gave
them a different perspective on things
it open doors that weren't open before
in their minds as far as the government
is concerned go
ahead
how how is our church
embroiled in a discussion about
vaccines when this is
happening how is
it that project
2025 this red wave
how is all this
happening but right now in our
church we're talking about
vaccines and what our church leadership
should have
done and creating a crisis in our
church while you barely hear a
peep about this Red Wave a red wave mind
you that I have set is coming for the
longest
time and many people were like oh and
you know what Co was you know what Co
was a test run
for Co was a test run for how many
people could Satan throw off track from
The Three Angels
messages how many people can I get to go
along the line of the seven how can I
how can I how can I low Adventist over
to the Seven Mountains and let them
begin to totally revamp and recalibrate
The Three Angels messages to be talking
about communism and Marxism and vaccines
and Global Elites and and socialism and
wokeism and critical race theory huhuh
that part so you're saying
that remaking the Three Angels message
or doing an amendment to bring those
into that's right that's wild that's
wild that is wild
and now when y'all see a red map how do
you explain the red map in light of this
threat for communism and Mar where's the
threat
what remember what the first piece did
I'm going to create a decoy and say no
that's the issue no no no the issues in
the past pism the issues in the in the
future futurism this is exactly what the
second beast did
and now many of us are like dear in the
headl like okay where do we go now with
this because you know what praise God I
have seen a lot of on and just to give
some of the other side on social media
Adventist you know talking about
Revelation 13 I mean you know they are
some eyes have been opened some eyes are
opening I should say or returning back I
however you want to say it it was
comforting to see and I mean I've seen
the other too but I've definitely seen
some saying like hm this looks very
Revelation 13ish so now that you can't
talk about the government because now
the government is Holy for for some of
us now the government is Holy now and
God is in control now and you know now
everything is aligned and as an adven is
I'm Blown Away how you could have gotten
to that mindset that now is now we're
good yeah but at least
now the actual danger is front and
Center
Stage yeah and nobody can deny it now
again this is not me saying this is all
going to happen in the next four years
that's not me saying that we don't know
what's going to happen in the next four
years somebody else could get in the
office in the next four years that all
I'm trying to say is look at the trend
that's all I'm saying yeah don't be
deceived by don't get de don't go after
the decoys
here this's what I want to show you
let's go to the screen real quick and
then go ahead you you share what you're
going to share I'm g go to the screen
I'm just thinking I I'm just thinking
but I it's it's too much to talk about
right now so let's go to the screen
let's go to the screen I need to show
you an example of what's coming y'all
I'm not saying it's coming in the next
four years but I just need you to see
what's coming so on the screen you have
you see a couple of faces first of all
there's a book called the case for
Christian nationalism published in 2022
by Steven wolf Steven wolf is one of the
one of the guys on the screen there you
will see of those six pictures uh those
six people are part of a a a group or
Ministry called they call them theob
Bros these are Christian nationalists
you can see that the guy in the top left
hand corner his name is Doug Wilson he
spoke at the national conservative
convention this year or last year okay
you can see him in an interview with
Tucker Carlson the guy in the middle at
bottom row that's Steven wolf and the
guy on top in the in the middle uh
Middle top top row
middle his name is is uh
Joel
webin now these are representatives of
Christian
nationalism one of the guys is on tuer
Carlson they're at the National
Convention this is no small thing I want
you to listen to to Rob to Joel Wellen
um web
in this interview adopt a distinctly pre
uh Christian Preamble and then all all
the Ten Commandments must be legislated
what what we've done is we thought the
second table of the law so second table
meaning Commandments 5-10 uh the
Commandments of God that pertain to our
horizontal relationship with our
neighbor like don't steal don't murder
these kinds of things we think that
should be legislated by the civil
magistrate but the first table of law
not that um but that's not true and I'm
not just talking about old Covenant
Israel in the Old Testament you look at
King Alfred you look at Constantine uh
you look at Richard the lionart you look
at Duke Godfrey who who chopped a a Turk
uh in half diagonally with one swing of
the sword these guys they legislated
both tables of the law that's where all
the prosperity comes from uh because you
can't hang in midair uh these second
table Commandments of don't steal from
your neighbor apart from have no other
gods before me idolatry is the head The
Fountain Head of the dream you cannot
have an idolatrous people and yet
somehow have a moral
people there there is no some people
like oh you know you're making a big
deal about project 2025 you're making a
big deal about Christian
nationalism um
it's
amazing it's amazing to
me how many broken
ankles are among us right
now this is a wakeup
call it is people have been saying
pastor you're being political and no
matter how much I'm like you guys I'm
not being
political I'm just saying this is what
prophecy says yeah but you know in
reality you're just being political no
I'm not being political I'm just saying
this is what America's going to do oh
you hate America no I don't hate America
this is just what oh you're woke no I'm
not being woke I'm just trying to oh
you're you're you're a Marxist people
put their own definition on on what woke
means because I I I I it means I I said
this I said this for years ago and I got
I didn't get in trouble but say Ellen
White was woke the four Founders were
woke meaning that they understood the
assignment and they understood what was
going on and they actively work towards
that that's
woke well we can say I'm awake but I
can't if I say and that the the
Superstition right of I'll be awake but
I won't be woke M it's like like come on
let's mhm let's be adults in the room
right right and what's happening is that
the spirit of polit what I have been
warning about is that the spirit of
Politics the spirit in the political
world has entered into the church so
now the same hate the same Zeal the same
you're against I'm against you and
you're against us the same I'm not
listening you anymore because that
Spirit has entered into the church
mhm mhm so
so
if with the vaccine our position
was don't take the vaccine if you don't
want to take the vaccine if you don't
want to don't condemn each other no
Pastor you were you pushed the vaccine
you were with the GC you were paid by
the pharmaceutical company you're
involved in phaia and I'm like really no
oh you're trying to rewrite your history
you're trying to you I got the receipts
I'm like really
and it is this mentality of just like it
doesn't M it's this dogged mentality the
same thing you see in the political
realm you are now seeing in the
church to the point where it has now
brought in a division within our church
that is absolutely so
unnecessary you so uncalled for but
because all the prognosticating of
what's going to happen as a result of
those who took this vaccine and and what
all of people I go people don't know
that I wrote I wrote letters of uh of uh
exemption for people who didn't want to
explain that though yeah what I said
this is not the church position but this
is this person's personal conviction and
I wrote letters like that people don't
know that I'm not broadcasting that but
they're like oh you were against the
vaccine and you didn't do this and you
didn't do that and again that's neither
here
what I'm trying to say is the attitude
that literally made
people
choose the seven Mountain
mandate over the Three Angels
mandate was absolutely
stunning and if you go back to if you I
mean we all saw it the the seven
Mountain mandate it all LED with fear of
you fill in the blank fear of and it
just kept going it it and lock into the
fear Satan is not the author of fear and
God is not the author of fear I'm sorry
Satan is I'm sorry God is not the author
of fear but Satan is um will cause us to
be fearful and when you get somebody to
be afraid you can make them almost think
and do
anything because they're afraid and
they're trying to survive so you put
them in a survival mode and
um yeah um
and okay I said that to say because to
me the true elephant in the room for
this situation is fear it's fear but
fear cause but fear allowed people who
would not maybe normally think this way
or react this way fear makes you do
do yes it made it made people be afraid
of um other cultures Taking Over
America which is racism and then
misogyny
meaning afraid
of a woman leader or being president um
if you see what I'm saying they had let
me back up they got them on the Fear
Part so they made them they made the
fear caused people to be um afraid of um
a woman being president
right and we're not even on this today
but what I'm saying is when you hear all
the things of how many times they called
her stupid or not intelligent and all of
those things so the fear is what
kidnapped them and then took them to to
to be like okay well you know she any
female let's did not even use her but
any per any female just wouldn't be
intelligent enough or smart enough to be
able to be that
position
fear that if this President is elected
mhm it's going to be a communist
takeover mhm
fear because she's not intelligent you
just fill in the blank it didn't
matter fear of a non-traditional fear of
the people coming in over the borders to
attack us and kill fear of all these
things now does it mean that people not
crossing the border and committing crime
no they are they are does
is there are there issues in our school
yes there are are there issues in our
media yes there
[Music]
is Jesus never called us to a cultural
War Jesus never called us to engage in a
battle for
Nations Jesus called us to engage in a
battle for hearts
and you don't win Hearts through the
government you don't win Hearts through
legislation you don't win Hearts through
Force listen
y'all
fear is the most powerful tool that
Satan of the
enemy and once I can instill fear of
that person and that and that's why you
you've what have I been talking
about a
system a system I'm not talking about
Christians I'm talking about a system
that is leading Christians to do things
in the name of Jesus that ought not to
be
done when we learn to
demonize people and people
groups you in a
WR the Bible is not demon iing people
it's demonizing a system
right right but the moment I
start yeah it it's so this is the bottom
line y' how did how did this
red this Red Wave happened how did how
is the Christian world in America saying
this is God this is
what their weapon was
fear fear of the media fear of a
communist takeover a Red Scare fear of
uh of of what's happening in our schools
fear fear fear fear fear and all the
time saying there's a communist
takeover and then
py look at the map y'all we're almost
all red I know I know I know but hey
it's how we win
votes it's how we it's how we get our
people in the
office right fear
all right and both political parties do
that yeah you know making you afraid of
the other
side but this as Bible believing
Christians as Adventists you should you
should see things more clearly we know
yeah we
know this person may be saying this and
that group may be saying that but we
know okay you're saying to be afraid of
this you're saying to be afraid of that
but we know where the real enemy is
right we know what the real enemy is and
for us to have been sidetracked in so
crazy a way that we were over these last
5 years six years is absolutely stunning
we have a blueprint God has given us a
blueprint shamed and we shouldn't it
yeah God has given us a blueprint so
Sher says uh and I want to ask that
question Pastor how would you answer
those who would say you're doing the
same creating
fear so excellent question mhm let's say
I just came out of the BL one's like you
know what I think Protestant America is
going to do X Y and Z right You' be like
Pastor where you getting that from
you're creating
fear but I haven't created that
scenario this is the Bible right this is
the great controversy right and what I'm
saying is we don't need we don't need to
be afraid of Communism or Marxism or any
of those things because that's not what
the Bible say the Bible says focus on
this power and even in that it's saying
you don't have to be afraid of that
power you know the truth you know what's
going on therefore you don't need to be
afraid because you know exactly what's
coming and you can be prepared for it
it's when we don't know what's coming
and when as the moment Adventist stepped
off of The Three Angels messages and
went to the seven Mountain mandate all
of a sudden now everybody was the enemy
and and now we couldn't trust anybody
not even the people in our church and
look at the leadership and that whole
Spirit of of fear and suspicion and
conspiracy mad boom entered into the
church people who who who listened to me
for years all of a sudden yeah I used to
like him but he no longer preaches the
truth he's been
indoctrinated
really I've been preaching the same
thing that I've been preaching since I
came into this church nothing has
changed for me what's new is
vaccinations what's new is global Elites
what's new is uh uh
um the Marxism and all Marxism that's
what's
new you go back and listen to my sermons
from from 20 years ago prophetic sermons
same thing nothing's changed with me
y'all
on paper nothing that's nothing's
changed in adventism Chang on paper
that's what adventism believes that's
what adventism
believes
however go behind many of our P go into
go look at many of our messages pets
some pulpits and
it's yeah the mark of the
vaccine
and the threat of Marxism and you know
pastors are are are over worrying about
apostate Protestant at project
2025 I you don't know I so I heard so I
heard keep an eye on it it may I heard
that a lot but
vaccines we've got to stand firm really
y
Marxism watch out for it it's a takeover
but project
2025 and again this is not us saying
project 2025 is going to implement the
mark of the beast we haven't said that
we have never said that what we've said
is look at where it's trending this is
not coincidence this is not no one is
saying oh it's going to H this is simply
saying you guys let's not get sham
gotted let's not get sidetracked now is
the time that we ought to be
trumpeting a warning about what we see
happening in front of us in terms of
apostate protestantism but instead what
is our church caught up
in some in our church
vaccination right we are literally
arguing and making videos about C
vaccination I'm still stunned
y'all yeah but anyway I'm done you can
be stunned and out of time at the same
time
yes yes um but we um are thankful that
you joined us for you know everybody's
mind was on this um because of the
election we just had on Tuesday um but
it's also just very important to um just
refresh our minds of what the Bible says
um that's very important and we don't
have to be afraid God is not the author
of fear um and so we don't have to be
afraid we just but we just need to know
what the truth is and follow that truth
um I think it's you know it's been
amazing good opportunities to witness I
mean this week I know to our two
youngest I've witnessed quite a bit
because they're very paying attention
and was able to just highlight some of
the prophetical things that maybe if
this didn't happen um in this way I
wouldn't be able to do that so I'm just
saying there's opportunities now this is
really a right time for us uh to be able
to witness um to others because
everybody's mind is like what is going
on yeah well you know because you know
you know the Bible you're supposed to
know so this is a great time to share
and I'll say This Then I then I'm
done so many out there in the world
right now are talking about project 2025
MH and they're all off on what they're
what they're warning against on the most
dangerous pieces the most dangerous
pieces of it yeah I agree nobody
but
us understands what this actually means
right but we're we're allowing the
secular people not allowing M but the
secular people are like the Rocks crying
out but they're not even crying they
don't they themselves don't even
understand the the
significance of this thing right and
we're silent mhm this is not of time to
be silent it is we don't want to look
like we're against Evangelical
Christians because then that'll make us
look like we're woke and we're yeah and
we're Marxist yeah that is absolutely
crazy right how is this even how is this
happening like what are aen what are
Aven what are you GNA say if project 20
project 20 five gets you know is in the
POS well they are in the position to do
what they want to do but if they're they
they are one of their key things is turn
this country back to God or we need to
this worship on Sunday um and it gives a
little amendment that if you have
another day you'd like to worship on but
that's just a um a gift from the
government but what are avenus going to
say the government shouldn't be in that
position to give an amendment and a gift
of if you want to worship on another day
that's not the government's um role yeah
and Advent are arguing it's not a big
deal 2025 because they put the clause in
there it is a big deal because what if
somebody doesn't want to worship at all
they don't want to believe in God or
Jesus and not go to church at all they
have the right not to do that how are we
excusing and finding reasons to say
don't worry about project 2025 but when
the pope sneezes we're all like Sunday
law because they forget that America
gives power
anyway there yes well guys as you could
see we could go on and on and on and
you're so over time
idolatry of a Nation will lead you to
choose
Barabas over Jesus mercy and that is the
title of my sermon coming up Barabas the
problem with main with the problem with
today's
Christianity don't be thinking oh he's
about to just listen just calm and stay
and listen to the message amen all right
amen thank you again for for joining us
for Sabbath school don't go away because
it is not over there are more blessings
coming and we are thankful that you are
here I did see some first timers so
definitely welcome again to living Mana
church and we have some membership
transfers so after we we pray we want to
welcome some new people to living Mana
Church let's pray heavenly father thank
you for this study today Lord I pray
Lord that eyes will be opened I pray
Lord that ankles will be healed Lord
please help us to get help those who are
on the seven Mountain mandate Lord Lord
to get off of those
mountains and return to the Three Angels
mandate amen The Three Angels messages
please
Lord forgive us for being
sidetracked for following
decoys and Lord May our May our
Ministries and our
messages be calibrated
again upon the Three Angels messages
this we pray in Jesus name amen amen
amen
all right guys we are
excited I need glasses right now for
this
one looking small here okay so we have
some second readings and first readings
so I'm going to do the first readings
first and then we'll go